[{"answer": "I drove to West Virginia today, Piers, so I'm feeling very good right now.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "How are you feeling after all this?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "First of all, they tell me how bad things looked on what they've seeing.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What kind of pledges can you give going forward?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Piers, the only thing I can tell you is without trying to find some (inaudible) or whatever some words that would describe it.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "I mean, what is your view if you were being this passionate about it?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, I know Ted.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "What are you going to do about this young renegade who doesn't really care about being reasonable?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Cory is going to be welcome (ph) edition.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What about putting him on Cruz point man to point man?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Is that your take on the whole thing?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think he is particularly dangerous unless the American people find his message accurate.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "How can he be stopped and how dangerous and how potentially powerful is he as a rival faction to moderate (ph) republicans?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "... could he still work the system to force one?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "It's nice to be here.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "How (inaudible) are you?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "EINER: Well, unfortunately I don't see a dynamic that it changes all that much.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Why did it come to this and how do we avoid happening all over again in January?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, there's two things here that makes me laugh.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "What do you want to say to this?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, I see no reason why this dynamic won't play out in the primary context.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Is it Chris Christie or is it actually potentially someone like Ted Cruz?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you look at Ted Cruz and what he could have.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "And if so, does he deserve more support about it getting right now?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I have to wrap it up there.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "The question is who can do that?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "That is something that I tell him when he threw something in school.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "How did you come up with that message?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Do you believe in your heart after all this time that he's still alive?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "I feel that someone has him and holding him because there's not a surveillance tape around that shows him at all in a train station, out walking in the street, anywhere.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "What do you feel in your gut?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "If he was down there, with all the attention that is now received, do you believe that he would've been discovered now, is that's why you feel he must have been taken against his will?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Do you believe Vanessa that the school was negligent?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "They should never let him out of the school, it should have been impossible?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Even though he's 14, it shouldn't matter.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "I mean, do you think that could have happened?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "My message to my son is, that I love him and we'll going to find him, you'll come home to your family.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Vanessa, if by any chance he's able to watch this interview either now or when is replayed perhaps tomorrow or somebody who was holding him as you believe is watching you, what would your message be first to Avonte and then to perhaps somebody who maybe holding him?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Well, actually we did make a difference.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "So, Star Jones would it (ph) been better off to kick all the men out of the rooms here in Washington and let the women trash (ph) it out or is that just a terrible cliche that actually (inaudible) wouldn't have actually made any difference?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I think you're totally sexist.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Oh you wouldn't?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Well, there's no question.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "And all women is instinctive (inaudible) you think less testosterone field?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Let me hear what you got to say.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "I tell you what?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "You have to be pragmatic.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Well, you're saying that the have a lion share of the practicality of the household, right?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "... how we've been.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Did you see that?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "I don't think Kay Bailey Hutchison knows who is calming down the fight.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "What you make of Ted Cruz down in Texas?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I think that Ted Cruz is very focus on Ted Cruz.", "docId": "131017pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Do you not believe that Ted Cruz is sincere?", "qSentId": 622}]